이상하다, 어젯밤 어쩌다가
조이와 찰리가 키스하게 됐지?
It's so weird. How did Joey
end up kissing Charlie last night?
난 오빠가 찰리와
키스할줄 알았는데
- I thought you'd end up kissing Charlie.
- I thought I'd end up kissing Charlie too.
나도 그런줄 알았어!
하지만 세상은 요지경인걸!
But surprise!
난 파티 끝날때 가서
잘 모르겠어
I missed most of the party.
찰리가 여자지?
Charlie's a girl, right?
우리과에 새로 온 교수야
나랑 키스 안한 여자고
Yeah, she's this new professor
in my department that I did not kiss.
조이가 왜 그 여자랑 키스했지?
그많은 여자들 놔두고 말야!
I don't know why Joey had to kiss her.
Of all the girls at the party, God!
- 네가 왜 그렇게 신경써?
- 그래, 네가 왜 신경쓰니?
- Why do you care so much?
- Yes, Rachel. Why do you care so much?
로스는 우리 엠마의
아빠니까 그렇지
Because Ross is the father of my child.
난 로스가 많은 여자들을
만났으면 좋겠거든
You know, and I want him
to hook up with lots of women.
그리고 조이와 찰리는
공통점이 하나도 없잖아
All I'm saying is, I don't think that Joey
and Charlie have anything in common.
글쎄, 서로의 편도선에는
공통적으로 관심을 보이던걸?
I don't know. They seemed to have
a shared interest in each other's tonsils.
와, 조이와 교수라니!
만약에 둘이 아이를 낳았는데
Wow. Joey and a professor.
Can you imagine if they had kids?
찰리의 지성과 조이의 원초적인
And if the kids got her intelligence..
성적매력을 갖췄다고 생각해봐
and Joey's raw sexual magnetism..
공부벌레에 인기도 많겠네!
those nerds would get laid!
로스, 두사람 일 괜찮아?
All right. So, Ross, you're
okay with all this? I mean..
찰리와 안지 얼마 되지도
않았는걸, 난 괜찮아
It's no big deal.
I just met her. I'm fine with it.
이런! 찰리가 얼마나
매력적인지 잊고 있었어!
God, I forgot how hot she was.
- 커피 더 가져와야겠다
- 어서와
I'm gonna get some more coffee.
- 나도 같이가요
- 그래요
- Oh, you know, I'll come with you.
- Okay.
- 교수님이라며?
- 그래, 정말 멋져, 얼마나 똑똑하다구
- So a professor, huh?
- Yeah. She is cool. And she's so smart.
그리고 마음이 정말 '신랄'해
Her mind is totally acrimonious.
이렇게 쓰는 단어가
아닌가 보지?
Guess that's not how she used it.
설명을 해야할것 같아요
I feel like I owe you an explanation.
난 원래 파티에서 만난 남자와
막 키스하는 타입은 아녜요
I don't ordinarily go around
kissing guys at parties.
솔직히..
I'm..
좀 창피하네요, 날 한심하게
생각하지 말아줬으면 좋겠어요
Well, I'm kind of embarrassed.
I really hope you don't think less of me.
천만에요! 난 찰리를
한심하게 생각하지 않아요
Think less of you? No.
I don't think less of you.
마음에 드는 사람을 만나서
키스를 한거잖아요
I mean, you saw someone you liked
and you kissed them.
오히려 좋은사람 만나고도
키스 안하는 사람들
Those people who like someone
and don't kiss them..
그 사람들이 바보예요
그런 사람들 정말 싫어요
those people are stupid.
I hate those people.
나 스스로도 놀라고 있어요
Actually, I'm a little surprised at myself.
조이는 전에 만났던
남자들과 전혀 다르거든요
I mean, Joey's so different
from the guys I usually date.
모두 교수에 지식인이었죠
대부분 고생물학자였구요
They're all professors, intellectuals.
Paleontologists mostly.
- 알다시피 아주 지적인..
- 어떤 타입인지 잘 압니다
- You know, very cerebral..
- Yeah, I know the type.
일하러 가기전에 뭐좀 먹으려면
지금 '신랄'한게 좋겠어요
If we want to grab a bite before work,
we'd better get acrimonious.
틀렸어요?
점점 비슷해지기는 해?
No? Am I getting close?
프렌즈 시즌 9
'임신테스트'
- 안녕
- 어서와
- Hey!
- Hi.
내가 뭐 샀는지 보여줄게
Hey, you guys.
Look what I just got.
와! 예쁘다!
어디서 샀어?
Oh, wow! I love those!
Where did you get them?
인터넷 경매 사이트에서 샀어
I bought them off eBay. They used
to belong to the late Shania Twain.
샤니아 트웨인이
죽기전에 신었던 거래
피비, 샤니아 트웨인은
살아있어
Phoebe, Shania Twain is still alive.
그럼 나 바가지 쓴거네
Oh, then I overpaid.
이게 뭐야?
Hey, what's this?
소호에 새로 생긴
마사지샵 무료 이용권이야
Oh, it's a gift certificate
to this new spa in SoHo.
피비한테 보여주지마
그런 큰 마사지샵 체인을 혐오하잖아
You can't show Phoebe this.
She hates those corporate massage chains.
마사지도 받지 말라는 거야?
What, now I can't get a massage?
피비는 싫어하는게 너무 많아!
There are so many things
that she disapproves of.
피비 때문에 송아지 고기도
못 먹지, 모피도 못 입지
I can't eat veal. I can't wear fur.
사냥도 못하지
I can't go hunting.
- 너 사냥하고 싶니?
- 선택권을 갖고 싶다는 거야
- Do you want to go hunting?
- I would like to have the option.
이게 뭐야?
What's that? Hey, Rachel?
여기 절대가면 안돼!
No, you can't go there!
내가 이런 큰 마사지샵을
어떻게 생각하는지 알잖아!
You know how I feel about
these big massage places.
이런곳 때문에 나 같은 사람이
일자리를 잃는다구!
They're putting people like me
out of business.
얘 사냥도 하고 싶대!
She wants to go hunting too!
피비! 이거 썩히기 싫어!
Phoebe, come on,
I don't want to waste it.
100달러를 버리는 셈이라구!
It would be like throwing
away 100 bucks.
돈은 중요한게 아냐!
Okay, this is not about the money. Okay?
그런곳은 우리 심장을 파괴하고
It's about corporate greed
destroying our hearts..
우리를 빈 껍데기로 만든다구!
and leaving us hollow shells.
난 그런거 상관없어
I don't care about any of that.
그럼 우정은?
나한테 이 문제는 정말 심각해
Well, do you care about friendship?
I feel really strongly about this.
제발 이거 쓰지마!
친구로서 부탁할게
Please don't use this gift certificate.
I'm asking you as a friend.
오! 그놈의 '친구'!
Oh, not as a friend. Phoebe!
알았어! 안쓸게!
Fine. I won't use it.
- 약속해?
- 약속해
- Promise?
- I promise.
- 고마워
- 대신 사냥은 갈거야!
- Thank you.
- Well, I am going hunting.
안녕? 보고싶었어
Hey, honey. I missed you today.
- 그래?
- 그럼
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah. Hey.
- 오늘 저녁에 뭐하고 싶어?
- 글쎄, 이건 어때?
- What do you wanna do tonight?
- Oh, well, maybe we could..
집 어지르는 것으로
날 유혹하겠다구?
Okay, trying to turn me on
by making a mess?
마누라를 그렇게 몰라?
Know your audience.
그리고 내일 우리
불임검사 받기로 했잖아
Besides, tomorrow we're doing
those fertility tests.
그때까지 자기 올챙이들은
잘 간직하고 있어
Until then, you need to keep
your tadpoles in the tank.
그 검사 꼭 해야해?
Do we really need to take those tests?
그사람들이 쓰는 단어들이 싫어
I don't like the words they use,
you know?
너무 의학적이잖아
이건 '피피' 그건 '후후' 라고
They're so clinical.
This is a pee-pee, that's a hoo-hoo.
우리 아기 가지려고
노력한지 1년이 넘어
We've been trying
to have a baby for a year.
아무 이상 없는지
확인해 보는게 좋잖아
I think it's a good idea
to find out if everything's okay.
- 검사 몇가지만 받으면돼
- 컵에다가 그러기 싫단 말야
- Just a few routine tests.
- But I don't want to do it in a cup.
- 그게 뭐 어때서?
- 이상하잖아! 거긴 병원이라구
- What is the big deal?
- It's weird! You're in a doctor's office.
병원에서 하는건 이상하고
It's not okay to do it
in a doctor's office..
타코벨 주차장에서
하는건 괜찮아?
but it is okay to do it in
a parked car behind a Taco Bell?
로스가 그얘길 했단 말야?!
I cannot believe Ross told you that.
분명히 말하는데..
거긴 웬디스였어!
And in my defense, it was a Wendy's.
나도 내키지 않아
Look, I don't want to do
these tests either.
하지만 하는게 좋다고 생각해
But I really do think
it's a good idea.
하긴 초콜릿공장
I'm sure a doctor's office
can't be worse..
단체 견학가서
하는 것보다는 낫겠지
than on a class trip
to the Hershey factory.
그래! 레이첼도 다 얘기했어!
Oh, yeah! Rachel talks too!
와인이 우유보다 비싸다고
누가 그랬어?
Who says wine has to cost
more than milk?
- 안녕!
- 안녕
- Hey!
- Hi.
- 어때요?
- 좋아요
- Come on in. How are you?
- I'm good.
- 한잔 줄까요?
- 고마워요
- Can I offer you a drink?
- Please.
정신없는 하루였어요
I have been crazed all day.
학장님면담에 강의계획서에
I had a meeting with the dean,
my syllabus for summer school's due..
친구책에 넣을 글까지 썼거든요
and I'm writing the foreword
for a book.
나도 정말 바쁜 하루였어요
촬영장에 가보니까..
I had a pretty hectic day at work too.
Today I had to open a door and go:
뉴욕에 오게 돼서 너무 신나요
So I am just so excited to be here.
- 빨리 여기저기 가보고 싶네요
- 안내가 필요하면 얘기해요
- I can't wait to explore the city.
- If you need a tour guide..
정말이에요?
그럼 정말 재밌겠네요
Oh, you mean it?
That would be so fun.
그럼요, 물론이죠
어디가고 싶어요?
Oh, yeah, definitely. Definitely. Okay.
What do you want to see first?
에이버리 피셔 홀에서 크로노스
현악 4중주단 공연이 있대요
We could go see the Kronos Quartet
at Avery Fisher Hall.
알았어요
Okay.
공립 도서관에서 월트 휘트먼의
편지를 전시한다더군요
There's a collection of Walt Whitman
letters on display at the public library.
네, 알아요
I know.
하지만 그보다 먼저..
'메트'에 가고 싶어요
- But first, I have to see the Met.
- Okay, let me stop you right there.
잠깐 내말 들어봐요
'메츠'는 형편없어요
The Mets suck, okay?
'양키즈'를 보러갑시다
You wanna see the Yankees.
아뇨, '메트'
복수가 아니라 단수요
No. No, not the Mets.
The Met. Singular.
누구요? 선수 하나하나
다 형편없다니까요
Which one? They all suck.
미술관 말이에요
The museum.
내 생각은 달라요
I don't think so.
- 안녕하세요?
- 안녕하세요
- Hi there.
- Hello. Welcome to Lavender Day Spa.
라벤더데이 스파에
잘 오셨어요
뭘 도와드릴까요?
How may I help you?
레이첼 그린으로
마사지 예약했는데요
Hi. I have a massage appointment
under Rachel Greene.
- 알겠습니다
- 무료 이용권이에요
- Okay.
- And here is my gift certificate.
- 찢어졌네요?
- 그래서 다시 붙였어요
- This has been torn up.
- And taped back together.
준비되는 대로
불러드리겠습니다
Okay. Well, I'll call you as soon
as your massage therapist is ready.
- 알았어요
- 유리문 안쪽에서 기다리세요
- Okay.
- Have a seat through the glass doors.
- 유리문 안쪽이요?
- 유리문 안쪽이요
- Through the glass doors.
알았어요
All righty then.
피비, 손님이
대기실에서 기다리세요
Phoebe, your next client's
in the waiting room.
다른 사람들 없을때도
그런식으로 말해야 해요?
Do we have to talk like that
when they're not around?
오, 이런! 맙소사!
Oh, no. No, no.
저 손님 다른 사람이
맡으면 안돼요?
Listen, is there someone
who can fill in for me?
전부 예약이 돼있어요
- Sorry. Everyone is booked.
- That woman can't know I work here.
나 여기서 일하는거
저 여자가 알면 안돼요
내 친구인데 내가
이런 큰 마사지샵엔
She's a friend of mine
and I made this big stink..
절대가지 말랬거든요
about how awful
these massage chains are.
- 피비는 왜 여기서 일해요?
- 돈 많이 주잖아요
- Then why do you work here?
- Because it's good money.
그래도 여기가
But that doesn't change the fact..
사악한 곳이라는 사실은
변함없어요!
that this is an evil,
bloodsucking corporate machine.
난 좋은 직장이라고
생각하는데요?
Well, I think this is a great place
to work.
아, 도청장치가 돼있나요?
Okay, are they listening?
- 로스?
- 어서와
- Ross. Hey.
- Hi.
찰리에 관해 할 얘기가 있어
I need to talk to you about Charlie.
정말? 꼭 해야해?
Oh, do you? Do you really?
그래, 나 고민이 생겼어
Yeah, I'm kind of having
a little problem.
'신랄'이라는 단어를 모르면
그냥 쓰지마
Look, if you don't know what the word
"acrimonious" means, just don't use it.
그게 아냐
Look, you know Charlie, right?
찰리는 멋있고 재미있고
몸매는 완전히..
- She's cool, funny, her body is so..
- Get to the problem.
본론만 얘기해
찰리는 내가 지금까지
만난 여자들
Right. She's just so much smarter
than all the girls I've ever dated.
합친 것보다도 똑똑해
Combined.
찰리가 날 멍청하다고
생각하지 않았으면 좋겠어
You know? And I just..
I don't want her to think I'm stupid.
너 허리띠 두개 했니?
Are you wearing two belts?
어라? 정말이네!
Hey, what do you know?
멍청하게 보이기 싫다는
얘기까지 했어
You were saying you didn't want
to seem stupid.
맞아, 찰리가 문화공간에
가고 싶어해
Well, she wants to go
to all these cultural places..
그 분야는 아는게 없잖아
네가 좀 도와줘
and I don't know how to talk about
that stuff. You gotta help me out.
난 정말 두사람 관계에
관여하고 싶지 않아
I don't want to get involved
in your guys' relationship.
부탁해, 넌 내가 아는 사람중에
제일 똑똑한 사람이야
Oh, dude, please. Come on,
you're the smartest person I know.
찰리가 정말 마음에 들어
놓치고 싶지 않아
And I really like this girl, okay?
I don't want to lose her.
- 알았어
- 고마워
- Fine.
- Thanks.
좋아, 생각해보자
Okay. Let's see.
- 아! 메트에 데리고 가!
- '메츠'라고 해야지!
- Oh, you should take her to the Met.
- The Mets.
아니, 메트
메트로폴리탄 미술관 말야
No, no, no. The Met.
The Metropolitan Museum of Art.
아, 찰리가 말한게 그거구나!
Oh, that's what she meant.
줄여서 부르려면
'미관'이라고 하던가!
If they're gonna shorten it, they
should call it the "Muse," you know?
그래야 헷갈리지 않지!
Short for "museum"
and avoid all the confusion.
그래, 거기가면 헷갈려서 잘못
찾아온 성난 야구팬들로 북적거려
Yeah, most days the place is packed
with confused, angry baseball fans.
아무튼 좋아
메트에 데리고 갈게
Okay. All right,
so I'll take her to the Met.
그리고 매디슨 애비뉴에
근사한 희귀책 서점이 있어
Yeah. Okay. There's this great
rare bookstore on Madison Avenue.
그리고 찰리는 건축을
좋아하니까 이렇게 해봐
You know what?
She loves architecture.
5번가를 따라 걸어서
성 패트릭 성당까지 가는거야
You should take a walk down Fifth
to the St. Patrick's Cathedral.
거기 찰리가 좋아할 만한
작은 패스트리 가게도 있어
And there, there's this great
little pastry shop that she'd love.
네가 찰리랑 데이트해야겠다
Jeez. Sounds like you
should be going on this date.
그럴수 없잖아
But I'm not.
- 그리고 태국음식이 괜찮다면..
- 천천히, 천천히!
- And you know what..?
- Okay, slow down.
너무 빨라서 모르겠어
메트부터 다시 말해봐
You're going way too fast.
Okay? Just go back to the Met.
거기가서 내가 정확히
어떻게 해야하는 거야?
So you gotta tell me exactly
what to do there.
미술관에 들어가면
오른쪽으로 꺾어져
When you walk into the museum,
take a right, okay?
거기가 고대관이거든
That's the antiquities wing.
고대 이집트, 메소포타미아
비잔틴제국 등이 전시돼 있어
Ancient Egypt, Mesopotamia,
up to the Byzantine Empire.
좋아, 들어가서
오른쪽으로 가란 말이지?
Okay. So I walk in the door
and make a right.
왠지 기분이 이상해
내모습 몰래 찍어서
I have a weird feeling about
this place. How do I know..
인터넷에 뿌리지 않는다고
어떻게 믿지?
they won't secretly videotape me
and put it all over the lnternet?
그건 말야..
가능한 돌려서 얘기를 할게
Because, honey, and I mean this
in the sweetest way possible..
그런건 아무도
보고싶어하지 않아!
nobody's gonna wanna watch that.
챈들러 빙 씨?
여기 있어요
Mr. Bing? Here you are.
저방에 들어가서 이 용기에
표본을 담아오세요
Go into that room and deposit
your specimen into the container.
표본을 담으라구요?
Deposit my specimen?
그런말은 900번에
걸어야만 들을수 있던데
I usually have to call a 900 number
for that kind of talk.
알겠습니다
Thanks. Got it.
난 저쪽에서 검사 받아
All right. Honey, my tests
are down the hall.
- 정말 괜찮겠어?
- 괜찮아
- Are you sure you're gonna be okay?
- Yeah, I guess.
거북한 일이긴 하지만
신경쓸것 없어
Look, I know this is embarrassing,
but nobody cares.
여기에 자기 아는사람
아무도 없는걸
No one here even knows you.
오, 이런 맙소사!
Oh, my God!
정말 너무 하는군!
Oh, come on!
너무 재미있다!
How great is this?
우린 이상 없을거야
집에 가자
We're probably fertile. Let's go home.
여기 왜 온거야?
Why are you here?
남편이랑 한번 더 노력하려구
지난번에 문제가 있어서..
Sid and I are trying again
and we had trouble last time..
아니, 내말은 도대체 왜?!
이 여자가 대체 왜 여기있는 겁니까?
No, no, no. I mean, why?
Why is she here?
누구는 컵에다 하려니까
심통이 난 모양이지?
Oh, someone's a little cranky today
because they have to do it in a cup.
어머, 아동용 컵을 받았네?
Oh, they gave you the kiddie size.
뭐?
What?
안타깝지만 난
자궁 검사하러 가봐야겠어
This was fun. But I've got
an invasive vaginal exam to get to.
계속 있고 싶지만 나도
데이트 약속이 있어서..
I'd love to stay
but I've got a hot date.
가봐
도움이 필요하면 얘기해
Please go. Just let me know
if you need a hand.
의욕이 싹 사라졌어
I think it just fell off.
안녕하세요?
Hello, ja.
마사지 받으실 시간이에요
It's time for your massage, ja?
얼굴을 구멍에 넣으세요
Put your face in the hole.
진짜 스웨덴 사람이 해주는
스웨덴식 마사지네!
A Swedish massage
from a real Swedish person.
좋아요, 난 스웨덴 사람이에요
Okay, then I'm Swedish.
이름이 뭐예요?
So, what's your name?
평범한 스웨덴식 이름이에요
It's a normal Swedish name.
아이키아
Ikea.
- 와, 재미있는 이름이네요
- 네
- Wow. What an interesting name.
- Yeah.
- 난 말이죠..
- 두피 마사지 해드릴께요
- You know, I..
- Time for your scalp massage.
와! 참 예쁜..
Wow. I really love your..
- 뭐 잘못됐나요?
- 아뇨
- Is something wrong?
- No, it's just..
기분이 좋아서요
It just feels so good..
아이키아!
Ikea.
물론 잘 알고 있겠죠?
스웨덴의 수도가 어디죠?
Hey, say, you'll know this.
What's the capital of Sweden?
스톡홀름이죠
Stockholm.
젠장! 맞는지 안맞는지
알수가 없잖아!
Damn. I wish I knew
if that was right.
화가 특유의 선과
임파스토 기법을 주시하세요
Note the painterly lines
and subtle impasto on this canvas.
모네는 신속하게
야외에서 그림을 그렸다는데요
Monet painted quickly,
and usually outdoors..
그의 주제가
빛 자체였기 때문이죠
as his elusive subject was light itself.
네가 방금 한말이
무슨 뜻인지는 알아?
Now, do you have any idea
what you just said?
입으론 대사를 읊지만
머리론 괴물의 몸통을 생각하지
No, no. My mouth says the words,
my brain is thinking "monster trucks."
그리고 모네는
Now, remember,
when you get to the museum..
M-O-N-A-Y가 아냐
그건 널 위해서 내가
Monet is not spelled M-O-N-A-Y.
I just..
- 발음표기법으로 쓴 거야
- 발음표기?
- I wrote that out phonetically for you.
- Phonetically?
그래, 무슨 말이냐 하면..
아니, 그거 설명할 시간 없어!
Yeah, that means..
We just don't have time for this.
그나저나 이 많은걸 그렇게
빨리 외우다니 놀랍다
I gotta say, I'm really impressed you
were able to memorize all this so quickly.
난 배우야
외우는덴 자신있다구
I'm an actor.
I can memorize anything.
지난주에 드라마에서
Last week on Days, I had to say:
"전측두엽 관골 뇌수술"이란
대사도 했는걸
"Frontal temporal zygomatic craniotomy."
- 와! 그게 무슨 뜻이야?
- 나도 모르지
- Wow. What does that mean?
- No idea.
하지만 다음 장면에서 그 대사를
들은 상대역이 죽었어
But the guy I said it to
dies in the next scene..
내 생각엔 "곰한테 잡아먹힐 거다"
라는 뜻인거 같아
so I guess it means,
"You'll get eaten by a bear."
그래
Okay.
- 그럼 르네상스로 넘어가자
- 알았어
- So let's move on to the Renaissance.
- Okay.
카라바지오는 중심인물의 고뇌를
Caravaggio uses chiaroscuro here..
강조하기 위해 명암법을 썼죠
to highlight the anguish
of the central figure.
만져봐요
진짜 울퉁불퉁해요
Touch it. It's really bumpy.
안돼, 안돼! 애드립 넣지마!
그리고 그림은 만지면 안돼!
No, no, no. No ad-libbing.
And, dude, you can't touch the paintings.
- 뭐 어때?
- 안돼!
- Come on.
- No. No!
제 표본은 방안에 있습니다
My specimen's in the room.
안에 있는동안 문 두드린 분이
누군지 모르지만 감사 드리고 싶네요
I just want to thank whoever knocked
on the door while I was in there.
덕분에 신속하게
처리할수 있었어요
Really helped speed the process along.
재니스, 아직도 안갔어?
Janice, you're not gone?
남편이 안나왔어
Sid is still in his room.
집에선 포르노를 못보게 하니까
지금 신났을 거야
I don't allow porn at home,
so this is like a vacation for him.
그래서 잘했어?
So did you do it?
Did you make your deposit?
- 그래, 이제 어려운 일은 끝났어
- 그건 어려운게 아냐
- Yeah. The hard part's over.
- That's not the hard part, honey.
맞아, 당신이랑 대화를 해야하니깐
하지만 모니카가 나오면
No, there's talking to you,
but Monica's coming out.
우린 갈거야
And we're gonna go soon.
챈들러
Chandler.
어려운건 그 다음이라구
결과가 어떨지 걱정안돼?
The hard part's what comes next.
Aren't you worried about the results?
지난번에 남편이랑 여기 왔을때
세상에.. 난 엉망이었어
I mean, oh, when Sid and I did this
last time, my God, I was a mess.
결과는 생각해본적 없는데?
I haven't even thought
about the results.
난 당연히 모든게
이상없을 거라고 생각했어
I just assumed everything
would be okay.
그래, 아마 그럴거야
Well, you know what? It probably is.
만약 아니면 어쩌지?
But what if it's not okay?
문제가 있어서
아기 못가지면 어떡해?
I mean, what if there's a reason
we can't have a baby?
자기랑 모니카는 아기를
꼭 낳게 될거야
Chandler. Look, you and Monica
are meant to have children.
이상 없을테니 걱정말라구
I'm sure it's gonna be just fine.
그래, 고마워
그부분은 전혀 생각 못했어
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Thanks. I can't
believe I didn't even think of that.
단지 여기와서..
그걸 해야한다는 것만 걱정했지
I guess I was so worried about
having to come here and do that.
타코벨 주차장에서
하는건 괜찮고
You can do it
in a Taco Bell parking lot..
병원에서 하는건 싫어?
but you can't do it
at a doctor's office?
웬디스였다니까!
It was a Wendy's!
이게 스웨덴 국가예요
물어봐 줘서 고마워요
And that's the Swedish national anthem.
Thank you for asking.
와, 아이키아
Wow, Ikea.
멋진 문화군요
What a rich culture.
참, 내친구 중에도
마사지사가 있어요
You know what?
I have a friend who's a masseuse.
- 그래요?
- 그런데 실력은 별로예요
- Oh? Ja, ja?
- Ja. She's not very good, though.
- 그래요? 왜 그렇게 생각하죠?
- 글쎄요
- And why do you think that is?
- I don't know.
청승맞은 기타연주 때문에
Maybe it's because she's got
such callousy fingers..
손에 못이 박혀서 그런것 같아요
from playing crummy guitar.
손님이 워낙 까다롭고 쫀쫀해서
Or maybe she has trouble
loosening your knots..
마사지하기 힘든건 아닐까요?
because you're such
a high-maintenance tight-ass.
- 피비!
- 난줄 알았어?
- Phoebe!
- You know it's me?
아까부터 알고 있었어
Well, for like a half an hour!
스웨덴에 대해
거짓말 잘도 하더라
Man, you can lie about Sweden!
여기 왜왔어?
How can you come here?
- 여기서 일한다는 말 왜 안한거야?
- 너한테 일일이 다 말할 필요 없잖아!
- Why didn't you tell me you work here?
- I don't have to tell you everything!
공짜 마사지 받는다고 죄인 취급
할거면 당연히 말했어야지!
You do if you're gonna make me feel
guilty for getting a free massage.
- 팁은 포함돼 있지않아
- 오!
Tip's not included.
여기서 일하는걸
대체 왜 숨긴거야?
Why did you lie to me
about working here?
창피해서 그랬어!
돈 때문에 영혼을 팔았잖아!
Because I was ashamed, okay?
I sold out for the cash.
여긴 의료보험, 치과진료보험에
퇴직연금까지 있거든
And they give me benefits, like medical
and dental and a four-oh-wunk.
넌 값을 지불하면 그만이지만
난 이 조직의 한패가 된거야
But, you know, you pay a price.
Now I'm this corporate stooge..
출근부도 기록하고
and punching a clock..
세금도 내야해!
and paying taxes!
그렇게 싫으면 당장
Phoebe, honey,
if you hate it so much..
나가서 그만두겠다고 해!
you should walk out there
right now and quit.
네 신념에 따라 살아야지
Be true to what you believe in.
넌 원칙이 있는 애잖아
내가 그걸 얼마나 존경하는데!
Honey, you have principles,
and I so admire that.
난 그런게 없잖니!
I don't have any.
그래, 네말이 맞아
그만 둘거야
You know what? You're right.
I am gonna quit.
- 내 삶을 되찾아야겠어!
- 잘 생각했어, 피비
- It's time I took my life back.
- Good for you, Phoebe.
혹시 저안에도 도청장치 돼있다면
내가 한말 진심이 아니에요!
If you guys have microphones in
there too, I didn't mean any of that.
사랑해요
I love you.
아하! 잡았다
죽어라, 죽어!
Got you! Die! Die! Die!
'로스 겔러 교수 올림'
Respectfully, Professor R. Geller.
- 어서 와요
- 안녕?
- Hey.
- Hi.
메트 관람 어땠어요?
Hey, how was the Met?
정말 굉장한 곳이더군요
The museum was amazing.
조이가 미술에 대해 잘알죠?
Yeah, Joey really knows his art, huh?
전혀 아니던데요
Not so much, no.
전부 외운것 같더라구요
He had clearly memorized
all this stuff to say..
어떤건 전혀 말이 안되던데요?
and some of it didn't
even make any sense.
- 무슨 소리예요?
- 거기없는
- What do you mean?
- Well, for one..
그림에 대해서도 막 얘기하던걸요
he was talking about paintings
that were nowhere around.
잠깐만요, 두사람 미술관에
들어가서 오른쪽으로 갔죠?
Wait a minute. When you guys walked
into the Met, did you go to the right?
- 아뇨, 왼쪽으로 갔어요
- 오, 이런, 조이!
- No. No, we went to the left.
- Oh, Joey, Joey, Joey.
그래도 두사람 재미있는
시간을 보낸것 같군요
Still, it seems like you guys
are having a great time together.
네, 재미있었어요
Yeah. Yeah, it's fun.
왜요?
What?
둘은 친구지만 나와는 그만큼
Actually, Joey's your friend..
가까운 사이가 아니잖아요
얘기하면 이상할것 같아요
and you don't know me that well.
It'd be weird.
조금은 알잖아요
그냥 얘기해봐요
Well, I mean, a little.
But no, what? Go on.
그게..
Well..
조이는 지금 나한테
맞는 상대가 아닌것 같아요
I'm thinking that maybe Joey
isn't the right guy for me right now.
좀더 공통점이 많은 사람이
You know, maybe I should
be with someone..
좋을것 같아요
무슨 뜻인지 알죠?
I have more in common with.
You know what I mean?
네
Yeah.
하지만 조이한테
Yeah, but you know what?
기회를 줘봐요
I think you should give Joey a chance.
멋진 녀석이에요
I mean, he's a great guy.
물론 미술에는 문외한이지만
And sure, he doesn't know
that much about art..
미술 얘기는 다른 사람과
언제든지 할수 있잖아요
but you can always talk about
that with someone else.
- 그건 사실이에요
- 생각해봐요
- I guess that's true.
- If you think about it..
조이가 그걸 다 외운건 그게 당신에게
중요하다고 생각했기 때문이에요
he memorized all that stuff because
he thought it was important to you.
조이는 그런 친구예요
You know, that's the kind of guy
Joey is.
네, 아주 자상하죠
He is very sweet.
그리고 섹시하구요!
Plus, he is hot!
그얘기도 막 하려던 참이에요
That was gonna be my next argument.
- 준비됐어요?
- 네, 가요
- You ready?
- Yeah. Let's go.
와!
Wow!
고마워요
- Thanks, Ross.
- Yeah.
로스? 미술관 작전 효과만점이야!
너 때문에 살았다
Hey, Ross. That art stuff worked.
You hooked me up.
도움이 돼서 기쁘다
Glad I could help, man.
어떤 작품들은 네가 말한곳에
없었지만 내가 잘 처리했어
Some of the stuff wasn't where you said
it would be, but I made it work.
지금 이걸보고 흥분되면
곤란하지!
It is not okay that I'm aroused
by this now.
여보세요?
Hello?
안녕하세요, 코넬리 박사님
Oh. Hi, Dr. Connelly.
지금 없는데요
들어오면
No. Well, she's not here..
제가 전해줄게요
but I can tell her.
앉아서 들어야 하나요?
Should I be sitting down for this?
그게 무슨 뜻이죠?
Well, so, what does that mean?
네, 알겠습니다
Okay. Okay, thank you.
고맙습니다
Thanks.
나 왔어
Hey, sweetie.
방금 코넬리 박사님이
전화했어
Dr. Connelly just called.
좋은 소식이야?
아닌가보구나
With good news?
Of course it's not good news.
방금 자기 말투 심각했어
You said, "Dr. Connelly just called."
좋은 소식이었다면
아주 방정맞게 말했을 텐데
If it was good, you'd have said,
"Dr. Connelly just called!"
뭐래?
So, what is it? Is it..?
문제가 있대?
나야? 아니면 자기야?
Is there a problem? Is there
a problem with me, or with you?
우리 둘다 문제가 있대
Actually, it's both of us.
뭐?
What?
내 정자는 운동성이 아주 낮고
Apparently, my sperm
have low motility..
자기는 임신이 되기에
'부적당한 환경'이래
and you have
an inhospitable environment.
그게 무슨 뜻이야?
Well, what does that mean?
내 정자들은 게을러 터져서
움직일 생각을 안하고
It means that my guys won't
get off their Barcaloungers..
자기 자궁은 내 정자가
오면 죽이려고 든대
and you have a uterus that is
prepared to kill the ones that do.
- 그말은..
- 챈들러?
- It means..
- Wait, Chandler.
계속 노력해볼수는 있지만
It means that we can keep trying..
임신이 안될 가능성이
아주 높대
but there's a good chance
this may never happen for us.
그럴리가!
Oh, my God.
마음이 아파
I'm sorry.
나도 그래
I'm sorry too.
그래도..
Well..
뭔가 방법이 있을거야
we're gonna figure this out.
그래
I know.
- 좋은 아침이에요, 피비
- 좋은 아침이에요, 접수담당
- Good morning, Phoebe.
- Good morning, receptionist.
오늘 스케줄 표예요, 첫번째 손님이
1호실에서 기다리세요
Here's your schedule for the day.
Your first client is in Room 1.
레이첼 그린?
망할 계집애! 또 왔어?!
"Rachel Greene."
Son of a bitch! She came back?
스코틀랜드 식
마사지 받을 준비 되셨나요?
Are you ready
for your Scottish massage?
얼굴을 구멍에
넣으세요, 아가씨!
Put your face in the hole, lassie!